Don't Come Knocking is a drama, western film directed by Wim Wenders.
Howard Spence has seen better days.
Once a big Western movie star, he now drowns his disgust for his
selfish and failed life with alcohol, drugs and young women.
If he were to die now, nobody would shed a tear over him, that's the sad truth.
Until one day Howard learns that he might have a child somewhere out there...
Howard, played by Sam Shepard.
Doreen, played by Jessica Lange.
Sutter, played by Tim Roth.
Earl, played by Gabriel Mann.
Sky, played by Sarah Polley.
Amber, played by Fairuza Balk.
Don't Come Knocking is a 2005 American western film directed by Wim
Wenders, and written by Wenders and Sam Shepard.
They had previously collaborated on the film Paris, Texas (1984).
It was submitted at the 2005 Cannes Film Festival.
The tone is emotional.